Contact

ogefunke@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/oluwafunkeelizabeth-elepe-rn-24144bb8 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Medical-Surgical Pharmacology

Languages

English (Full Professional) Yoruba (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)

Oluwafunke Elizabeth Elepe, RN

Staff Registered Nurse at Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas)

Dallas-Fort Worth Metroplex

Summary

Energetic and experienced registered Nurse who prides herself on the development of a nursing practices that delivers excellence in patient care and passionate in delivering an exceptional care to all patients ensuring compliance with corporate standards, policies and procedures.

To be a contributing member of an organization in improving health and well-being of patients, people, community and the world at large, and striving to add prolific value to the organization output.

Experience

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Staff Registered Nurse April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

North Richland Hills, Texas

13 weeks Contracts.

Neuro/Tele/ Medsurg

SavaSeniorCare Administrative Services LLC Assistant Director Of Nursing January 2018 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Dallas, Texas

Baylor Scott & White Health Registered Nurse September 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 5 months) Rowlett. Texas

Competent and knowledgeable in guiding patients and their families from the challenges that come along with the complex health care system.

Integrate discharge planning into the patient's daily care.

Collaborate with other members of the health care team.

Learn the use of technology, including new medical innovations.

Integrate research in relation to a diverse care needs

Integrate the best practice guidelines in relation to diverse clinical situations

Advocate for ethical, quality, and safe work setting

St. Lucie Medical Center
Certfiied Nurse Technician
June 2013 - April 2016 (2 years 11 months)
Port St. Lucie, FL

- Provides hands-on and routine care to patients in medical hospitals,
 elderly care facilities and assisting the Registered Nurse with some medical equipment and procedures.
- Assists with direct patient care procedures and related tasks; checks in patients, assists in obtaining patient histories, takes vital signs, prepares charts, and assists with medical examinations.
- Educates and advises patients on specified medical issues within established parameters.
- Performs routine specialized procedures, such as venipuncture, catheterization, and sterile dressing changes under established protocols.
- Records patients' current vital signs
- Displays professionalism while completing multiple urgent tasks in a timely manner
- Records all care information concisely, accurately and completely, in a timely manner, in the appropriate format and on the appropriate forms

Education

Indian River State College
Bachelor of Science (BSc), Nursing Science (2016 - 2018)

Keiser University-Ft Lauderdale

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)

Indian River State College

Associate's Degree, Premedical Sciences · (2012 - 2014)